(self.webpackChunk_N_E=self.webpackChunk_N_E||[]).push([[405],{48312:function(e,t,a){(window.__NEXT_P=window.__NEXT_P||[]).push(["/",function(){return a(96825)}])},31691:function(e,t,a){"use strict";var n=a(85893);a(67294);var i=a(55512),s=a.n(i),o=a(94184),r=a.n(o);let l=e=>{let{showOnlyRight:t=!1,showOnlyTop:a=!1}=e;return(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:r()(s().container,t?s().flip:null),children:a?(0,n.jsxs)(n.Fragment,{children:[(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:s().Rect}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:s().Elip})]}):(0,n.jsxs)(n.Fragment,{children:[(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:s().RectL}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:s().ElipL}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:s().ElipR})]})})};t.Z=l},96825:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t),a.d(t,{default:function(){return en}});var n=a(85893),i=a(9008),s=a.n(i),o=a(67294),r=a(25675),l=a.n(r),c=a(56481),d=a(80438),h=a(63432),u=a(89476),m=a(42403),p=a(60070),f=a(38627),_=a(29087),g=a(67610),y=a.n(g),w=a(88415),b=a(51639),v=a(909);let j=e=>{let{showRef:t}=(0,w.S)({style:y().animateLeft}),{showRef:a}=(0,w.S)({style:y().animateRight}),{showModal:i}=(0,c.d)(),[s,r]=(0,o.useState)(!1),g=()=>{i(v.g4,"Options to buy $SFUND from","medium")},j=()=>{var e;null===(e=document.getElementById("faq"))||void 0===e||e.scrollIntoView({behavior:"smooth"})};return(0,o.useEffect)(()=>{let e=/constructor/i.test(window.HTMLElement)||"[object SafariRemoteNotification]"===(!window.safari||window.safari.pushNotification).toString();r(e)},[]),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:y().container,children:(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:y().innerWrapper,children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:y().sideDetails,ref:t,children:[(0,n.jsxs)("h1",{className:y().title,children:["Join Best Web3 Gaming IGOs With",(0,n.jsx)("span",{className:y().blueTitle,children:"Seedify"})]}),(0,n.jsx)("p",{className:y().subTitle,children:"Decide your tier, stake or farm $SFUND, and participate in all the token launches we bring to you in a guaranteed way."}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:y().actionsWrapper,children:[(0,n.jsx)(b.Z,{label:"Buy $SFUND",color:"active",onClick:g,size:"md"}),(0,n.jsx)(b.Z,{label:"How to Start",size:"md",onClick:j})]}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:y().availableWrapper,children:[(0,n.jsx)("p",{className:y().available_text,children:"AVAILABLE ON:"}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:y().available_images,children:[(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:d.Z,alt:"Kucoin"}),(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:h.Z,alt:"Gate.io"}),(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:u.Z,alt:"Huobi"}),(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:m.Z,alt:"Bybit"}),(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:p.Z,alt:"Pancakswap"}),(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:f.Z,alt:"Uniswap"}),(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:_.Z,alt:"Camelot"})]})]})]}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:y().sideImage,ref:a,children:s?(0,n.jsx)("video",{src:"becomeInvestor/machine.mp4",autoPlay:!0,loop:!0,muted:!0}):(0,n.jsx)("video",{src:"becomeInvestor/machine.webm",autoPlay:!0,loop:!0,muted:!0})})]})})};var x=a(31691),k=a(80987),N=a.n(k);let S=()=>(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:N().container,children:[(0,n.jsx)(x.Z,{showOnlyTop:!0}),(0,n.jsx)("h2",{className:N().title,children:"How To Buy $SFUND"}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:N().borderFrame,children:(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:N().videoContainer,children:(0,n.jsx)("iframe",{title:"how to buy sfund",className:N().iframe,src:"https://www.youtube.com/embed/TL-6czMQ5Ac?showinfo=0",allowFullScreen:!0})})})]}),I=[{id:"purchase",icon:{src:"/_next/static/media/purchase-icon.2574b485.svg",height:60,width:60},title:"Purchase $SFUND Tokens",description:"$SFUND is Seedify's token that enables its holders to participate in IGOs, IDOs, INOs, stake and farm for passive income",action:{name:"Buy $SFUND",url:""}},{id:"stake",icon:{src:"/_next/static/media/stake-icon.65a2f88b.svg",height:60,width:60},title:"Stake or Farm your $SFUND",description:"Add your $SFUND to one of our staking or farming pools and earn passive income",action:{name:"Start Now",url:"https://staking.seedify.fund/"}},{id:"kyc",icon:{src:"/_next/static/media/kyc-icon.039dae53.svg",height:60,width:60},title:"Complete KYC",description:"It's a simple step to ensure your participation in our IDOs and IGOs (not necessary for INOs)",action:{name:"Register",url:"https://verify-with.blockpass.org/?clientId=seedifyfund_launchpad_kyc_cbe49&serviceName=Seedify.fund%20Launchpad%20KYC&env=prod"}},{id:"set",icon:{src:"/_next/static/media/allset-icon.fe17d868.svg",height:60,width:60},title:"You’re all set!",description:"Now you can participate in the sales for tokens and NFTs of the best blockchain projects"}];var F=a(54551),B=a.n(F);let G=()=>{let{showRef:e}=(0,w.S)({style:B().animateLeft}),{showRef:t}=(0,w.S)({style:B().animateRight}),{showModal:a}=(0,c.d)(),i=()=>{a(v.g4,"Options to buy $SFUND from","medium")};return(0,n.jsx)("section",{className:B().land_ing_join,children:(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:B().container,children:(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:B().inner_land_ing_join,children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:B().leftContainer,ref:e,children:[(0,n.jsx)("h2",{className:B().join_title,children:"How To Join The Web3 Gaming Revolution With Us"}),(0,n.jsx)("p",{className:B().join_text,children:"Only 3 steps are needed for you to start enjoying all the advantages of Seedify"})]}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{style:{overflowX:"hidden"},children:(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:B().join_map,ref:t,children:I.map(e=>(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:B().map_row,children:[(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:e.icon,alt:e.title,className:B().map_row_icon}),(0,n.jsx)("h4",{className:B().map_row_header,children:e.title}),(0,n.jsx)("p",{className:B().map_row_text,children:e.description}),e.action&&(e.action.url?(0,n.jsx)("a",{className:B().action_btn,href:e.action.url,target:"_blank",rel:"noreferrer",children:e.action.name}):(0,n.jsx)("button",{className:B().action_btn,onClick:i,children:e.action.name}))]},e.id))})})]})})})};var C=a(1198),T=a.n(C),R={src:"/_next/static/media/arrow.4ba48182.svg",height:11,width:16};let W={Basics:[{question:"What is Seedify?",answer:"Seedify is a leading incubator and launchpad for Web3 projects, which boosts top-tier blockchain initiatives, providing support in several fronts.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/introduction-to-seedify-fund-a411f9d792c"},{question:"How does the Launchpad work?",answer:"In this article we want to provide you answers to questions that you may have in mind, to help you understand everything about Seedify.fund Launchpad better.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/seedify-fund-launchpad-q-a-3bbf8ba616a3"}],$SFUND:[{question:"What are the utilities of $SFUND?",answer:"$SFUND is the token that empowers the entire Seedify ecosystem. Its main utilities are: participating in the IGOs and INOs hosted at Seedify, staking or farming to earn passive income, get free incubation tokens via the seed staking feature and use it for travel expenses and bookings at travala.com. The Seedify team is constantly working to bring more relevant utilities to $SFUND."},{question:"What should I do after purchasing $SFUND? Can I already join an IGO?",answer:"To start enjoying all the benefits of being an $SFUND holder, you need to stake/farm your $SFUNDs in one of the pools available and complete the KYC process (to participate in the IGOs). By having those steps done, you’ll be able to join the next IGO hosted on our platform and other benefits such as the Seed Staking and Staking/Farming rewards.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/updated-how-to-participate-in-initial-dex-offerings-idos-on-seedify-2ea3c6c6f492"}],$SNFTS:[{question:"What are the benefits of staking/farming $SNFTS?",answer:"Simply put, the act of staking and farming earns you more tokens! So instead of buying more you can lock away your $SNFTS and gain interest depending on the number of days you stake as per the staking pools. You can also gain access to Seedify’s Avatar Collection.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/how-staking-and-farming-snfts-gives-you-access-to-seedifys-avatar-nft-collection-d6ad62b8d98d"}],IGOs:[{question:"What is an IGO?",answer:"Initial Game Offerings or IGOs allow projects to raise funds and gain a base community of supporters, while providing gamers and game enthusiasts opportunities to purchase new gaming tokens before they’re listed on public exchanges.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/updated-how-to-participate-in-initial-dex-offerings-idos-on-seedify-2ea3c6c6f492"},{question:"What is the Viral Public Raise Model?",answer:"In a nutshell, the model revolves around making each raise more viral, giving also people with no $SFUNDs allocations from our IGOs in a lottery based manner, in ways we can introduce much more virality, adoption for games, buybacks from token price differences which will be deposited for $SFUND rewards to our stakers and farmers, in a different kind of pricing model for tokens which will always have people with $SFUNDs buy at a discount still with guaranteed allocations.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/seedify-viral-public-raise-model-8c14ac0e93a6"},{question:"How does the Seedify Incubation Program help IGO projects succeed?",answer:"Our primary mission for providing incubation services is to ensure that blockchain games with potential receive the correct guidance for a successful launch and beyond. Having successfully launched over 50 projects in blockchain gaming, we can provide a high level of expertise to increase the likelihood of a project’s success and a higher return for holders, players and partners.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/how-seedifys-incubation-program-helps-projects-succeed-9675764a8af1"},{question:"How can I get back the tokens purchased on an IGO?",answer:"After the IGO happens, the token purchased will be listed and only after the TGE (token generation event) $SFUND holders who purchased the tokens at the IGO will receive them. There are three ways holders get their tokens back: the first is via claim on Seedify’s claim platform, the second is via airdrop sent by Seedify team and the third is via claim on the project’s platform."}],INOs:[{question:"What is an INO?",answer:"INO stands for Initial NFT Offering and is an opportunity where users can purchase items from NFT collections before they are available to the public on the NFT marketplaces.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/seedify-ino-launchpad-your-guide-to-inos-and-participation-mechanics-3866f2dec516"},{question:"How should I select which NFT projects to buy?",answer:"There are several factors that contribute to an NFT project being successful, and a few ways to get your hands on an NFT, with the most desirable being minting. Unfortunately, it is not easy gaining the opportunity to mint an NFT, and it is normally often only available to people with a whitelist spot.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/what-to-look-out-for-when-choosing-an-nft-project-d1c497c74fb5"}],Blockchain:[{question:"What is Blockchain Gaming?",answer:"To be classified as a blockchain game, a project must use elements of the blockchain, such as NFTs and cryptocurrency. NFT technology allows players to trade their gaming assets such as weapons, clothes, vehicles etc. which in traditional games usually have no value outside of the game.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/the-past-present-and-future-of-blockchain-gaming-9d01bfe240f8"},{question:"How Do  I get Started with Blockchain Gaming?",answer:"For players to join games, in most cases they need to connect their Web3 wallets, such as MetaMask, to the game. This effectively acts as your login to the game and is where your rewards and in-game assets are stored for future gameplay or to be sold on marketplaces.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/what-is-blockchain-gaming-and-why-is-it-so-popular-63f91764f1d"}],Security:[{question:"What is KYC and how do I complete it on Seedify?",answer:"KYC’s abbreviation stands for “Know Your Customer”. Passing KYC usually requires 1-2 forms of valid identification. This is Anti Money Laundering’s (AML) first step of due diligence and is a way for exchanges to protect their users whilst also remaining compliant.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/what-is-kyc-and-how-to-complete-the-process-on-seedify-dd596735129b"},{question:"How do I make sure I store my tokens securely?",answer:"The old phrase “not your keys, not your coins” has been repeated across social media channels lately, which has driven many crypto holders to opt for non-custodial wallets. Custodial wallets are offered by platforms like centralized exchanges that store and protect the wallet’s keys. Since users do not have full control over their keys, they don’t have full control over their crypto.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/not-your-keys-not-your-crypto-how-to-store-your-tokens-securely-59232723c4a9"}],ProjectSelectionFramework:[{question:"How does Seedify select its projects?",answer:"Due diligence is very important to the quality and performance of the projects we work with. We recently overhauled our selection process, and now by cross-examining every report that is generated, we are much more risk-averse, eliminating all biases that a single team can have while focusing on the bigger picture more vividly.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/seedifys-upgraded-due-diligence-process-for-better-picks-a-new-feature-dfd541565987"}],SeedStaking:[{question:"What is Seed Staking?",answer:"We want to reward our most loyal community members with industry-leading rewards. We will do this by providing $SFUND stakers with free tokens from our incubated projects, and the projects to which we provide the most support.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/seed-staking-changing-the-launchpad-game-forever-2f2e9a319665"},{question:"What Are The Requirements for Seed Staking?",answer:"Since launching this innovative offering we’ve put together the most relevant FAQs to help you understand how the Seed Staking feature will work. Find out more about the requirements and details to get the most out of it.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/seed-staking-faq-all-you-need-to-know-about-seedifys-new-feature-c7cb0453f2ae"}],Web3Games:[{question:"What is the difference between Web2 and Web3 gaming?",answer:"To fully understand the main differences between traditional and blockchain gaming, let’s first look at the differences between Web2 and Web3 so we can understand how this can be applied to gaming.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/what-is-the-difference-between-web2-and-web3-gaming-8c2ece2a76b6"},{question:"What types of gaming projects can I expect on Seedify? ",answer:"At Seedify, we work day and night to instill mass adoption of the web3 gaming space. Game studios we are interacting with daily are on the same mission. There is an ever increasing number of professional game studios and teams that are choosing to build in this space. Here’s a look at some of the upcoming project types.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/lets-tell-a-new-storyweb3-gaming-with-seedify-91eeb779c33a"},{question:"What Are Storytelling NFTs?",answer:"Storytelling NFTs allows projects to build interest around their NFTs early and build a community to support their collection. Community collaboration is a really exciting part of storytelling NFTs. NFT holders can have the power to write the stories themselves or vote on what should happen next and contribute to the creative process of the story.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/transforming-storytelling-with-nfts-and-web3-caba815bc23a"},{question:"What is Seedify doing to change the Web3 Gaming industry?",answer:"Dive deeper into our historic bull run, the current state of web3gaming, and what Seedify is doing differently to change the game.",readMore:"https://blog.seedify.fund/the-game-791146ba13f1"}]},O=e=>{let{currentBTN:t}=e,[a,i]=(0,o.useState)(0),s=e=>{a===e?i(null):i(e)};return(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:T().container,children:W[t].map((e,t)=>(0,n.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:T().singleContainer,children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:T().question,onClick:()=>s(t),children:[e.question,(0,n.jsx)("span",{className:[T().arrow,a===t?T().arrowDown:T().arrowUp].join(" "),children:(0,n.jsx)(l(),{src:R,width:17,height:32,alt:"-"})})]}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:[T().answer,a===t?T().answerOpen:T().answerClosed].join(" "),children:[(0,n.jsx)("div",{style:{height:"5px"}}),e.answer," ",e.readMore?(0,n.jsx)("a",{className:T().readMore,href:e.readMore,target:"_blank",rel:"noreferrer",children:"Read more."}):""]})]}),(0,n.jsx)("hr",{className:T().hr})]},t))})};var L=a(58533),q=a.n(L);let D=()=>{let[e,t]=(0,o.useState)("Basics"),a=e=>{t(e)};return(0,n.jsxs)("section",{id:"faq",className:q().container,children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:q().mainBox,children:[(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:q().titleContainer,children:"Frequently Asked Questions"}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:q().description,children:["Haven't found the answers you are looking for? Contact us at"," ",(0,n.jsx)("span",{children:"support@seedify.com"})]}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:q().btnContainer,children:["Basics","$SFUND","$SNFTS","IGOs","INOs","Blockchain","Security","Project Selection Framework","Seed Staking"].map((t,i)=>(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:[q().btn,e===t.replace(/\s/g,"")?q().selected:""].join(" "),onClick:()=>a(t.replace(/\s/g,"")),children:t},i))})]}),(0,n.jsx)(O,{currentBTN:e})]})};var U=a(47724),M=a.n(U);let A=e=>{let{buttonText:t,url:a,actionText:i,filled:s}=e;return(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:s?M().filledContainer:M().container,children:[(0,n.jsx)("h5",{children:i}),(0,n.jsx)("a",{href:a,target:"_blank",rel:"noreferrer",children:t})]})};var E=a(30253),$=a.n(E);let P=()=>(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:$().container,children:[(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:$().RectL}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:$().ElipL}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:$().RectR}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:$().ElipR})]});var H=a(77334),Z=a.n(H);let K=()=>(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:Z().container,children:(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:Z().ElipL})});var Q=a(15328),Y=a.n(Q);let z=()=>(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:Y().marginContainer,children:(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:Y().container,children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:Y().subContainer,children:[(0,n.jsx)("h2",{children:"Guaranteed Refunds"}),(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"Public Seedify IGOs have a guaranteed refund policy of 7 or 14 days to keep a healthy balance between community needs and projects compliance."})]}),(0,n.jsx)("a",{rel:"noopener noreferrer",target:"_blank",href:"https://blog.seedify.fund/updated-seedifys-refund-policy-6e55476f558f",children:"Learn More"})]})});var X=a(48194),J=a.n(X),V=a(57861),ee=a(4832),et=a(43933);let ea=()=>{var e,t,a;let{data:i,isLoading:o}=(0,et.k5)(),{data:r,isLoading:l}=(0,et.Ep)(),{data:c,isLoading:d}=(0,et.eS)();return(0,n.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,n.jsxs)(s(),{children:[(0,n.jsx)("title",{children:"Seedify"}),(0,n.jsx)("meta",{name:"description",content:"Seedify NFT Games Launchpad"}),(0,n.jsx)("link",{rel:"icon",href:"/favicon.ico"})]}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:J().wrapper,children:[(0,n.jsx)(P,{}),(0,n.jsx)(j,{}),(0,n.jsx)(z,{})]}),o||l||d?(0,n.jsx)(V.Z,{}):(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:J().poolsContainer,children:[(null==r?void 0:null===(e=r.data)||void 0===e?void 0:e.length)?(0,n.jsx)(ee.Z,{title:"Live Pools",data:null==r?void 0:r.data}):null,(null==i?void 0:null===(t=i.data)||void 0===t?void 0:t.length)?(0,n.jsx)(ee.Z,{isUpcomingPool:!0,title:"Upcoming Projects",data:null==i?void 0:i.data}):null,(null==c?void 0:null===(a=c.data)||void 0===a?void 0:a.length)?(0,n.jsx)(ee.Z,{isCompletePool:!0,title:"Completed Pools",data:null==c?void 0:c.data}):null]}),(0,n.jsx)(S,{}),(0,n.jsx)(A,{url:"https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLiDBZC_egV5Xqn4nv2Gc_Lzsbg7ooOuTK",filled:!0,actionText:"Find out more about what you can do with $SFUND",buttonText:"Watch Videos"}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:J().wrapper,children:[(0,n.jsx)(K,{}),(0,n.jsx)(G,{})]}),(0,n.jsx)(D,{}),(0,n.jsx)(A,{url:"https://form.typeform.com/to/AcLYz4Wa",actionText:"Are you a web3 game studio looking to get incubated or launched by Seedify?",buttonText:"Apply now"})]})};var en=ea},55512:function(e){e.exports={container:"style_container__X4yvb",flip:"style_flip__YWC1B",RectL:"style_RectL__Mt0Lr",ElipL:"style_ElipL__BdFo3",ElipR:"style_ElipR__nPQvu",Rect:"style_Rect__m7Jn9",Elip:"style_Elip__3GtRc"}},47724:function(e){e.exports={container:"styles_container__vrTHl",filledContainer:"styles_filledContainer__cGyzo"}},15328:function(e){e.exports={marginContainer:"style_marginContainer__f1LUD",container:"style_container__3GKzU",subContainer:"style_subContainer__t_GfJ"}},80987:function(e){e.exports={container:"style_container__e4u1m",title:"style_title__dU6P2",borderFrame:"style_borderFrame__eOdxu",videoContainer:"style_videoContainer___tKg2",iframe:"style_iframe__8xdPI"}},58533:function(e){e.exports={container:"FAQ_container__phU_c",mainBox:"FAQ_mainBox__4h3hQ",titleContainer:"FAQ_titleContainer__x5sNc",description:"FAQ_description__12SZv",btnContainer:"FAQ_btnContainer__d7Exq",btn:"FAQ_btn__SfY0S",selected:"FAQ_selected__N06SE"}},1198:function(e){e.exports={container:"Accordion_container__lRo_z",singleContainer:"Accordion_singleContainer__bw4RR",question:"Accordion_question__RsDKg",answer:"Accordion_answer__HGRgp",answerOpen:"Accordion_answerOpen__h7sdm",arrow:"Accordion_arrow__cf_yG",arrowDown:"Accordion_arrowDown__zK1HZ",hr:"Accordion_hr__aYXsp",readMore:"Accordion_readMore__ICftE"}},67610:function(e){e.exports={container:"BecomeInvestor_container__WC2Zm",innerWrapper:"BecomeInvestor_innerWrapper__27jIA",sideDetails:"BecomeInvestor_sideDetails___0pU6",title:"BecomeInvestor_title__JBoeH",blueTitle:"BecomeInvestor_blueTitle__mYJd8",subTitle:"BecomeInvestor_subTitle__aMWGM",actionsWrapper:"BecomeInvestor_actionsWrapper__0c2xE",availableWrapper:"BecomeInvestor_availableWrapper__r3U2R",available_text:"BecomeInvestor_available_text__LbKCV",available_images:"BecomeInvestor_available_images__l5MJq",sideImage:"BecomeInvestor_sideImage__S1xJl",animateLeft:"BecomeInvestor_animateLeft__6tsba",animateRight:"BecomeInvestor_animateRight__6QR1l"}},30253:function(e){e.exports={container:"Background_container__KTfIm",RectL:"Background_RectL__oAOXA",ElipL:"Background_ElipL__xhjwR",RectR:"Background_RectR__egQgr",ElipR:"Background_ElipR__QBoro"}},54551:function(e){e.exports={land_ing_join:"BlockchainGaming_land_ing_join__5I85p",container:"BlockchainGaming_container__ZOODy",join_title:"BlockchainGaming_join_title__URK9_",join_text:"BlockchainGaming_join_text__tnwDk",join_btn_wrapper:"BlockchainGaming_join_btn_wrapper__1K31W",join_btn:"BlockchainGaming_join_btn__UJLr7",join_btn_selected:"BlockchainGaming_join_btn_selected__f175_",join_map:"BlockchainGaming_join_map__My9_s",map_row:"BlockchainGaming_map_row__nHPIH",map_row_icon:"BlockchainGaming_map_row_icon__vrgwb",inner_land_ing_join:"BlockchainGaming_inner_land_ing_join__zNhBh",leftContainer:"BlockchainGaming_leftContainer__vqGWQ",map_row_header:"BlockchainGaming_map_row_header__j2wi2",map_row_text:"BlockchainGaming_map_row_text__ppsFr",action_btn:"BlockchainGaming_action_btn__3OGiK",black:"BlockchainGaming_black__NqPO5",animateLeft:"BlockchainGaming_animateLeft__jfIXt",animateRight:"BlockchainGaming_animateRight__4ZVXi"}},77334:function(e){e.exports={container:"Background_container__X58l0",ElipL:"Background_ElipL__UA1xW"}},48194:function(e){e.exports={wrapper:"index_wrapper__tuStl",poolsContainer:"index_poolsContainer__Gig6U"}},9008:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(83121)}},function(e){e.O(0,[282,117,645,774,888,179],function(){return e(e.s=48312)}),_N_E=e.O()}]);